Narrator: 1
A: Have you done all your Christmas shopping?
B: Pretty much, apart from a few bits and pieces.
Narrator: 2
A: So do you consider the project to have been a success?
B: By and large. I think we achieved almost everything we set out to do.
Narrator: 3
F: You looked really fed up after the meeting.
M: Yes, I’m sick and tired of being put down every time I make a suggestion.
Narrator: 4
A: How often do you visit your parents?
B: I see them on and off, but not as much as I should.
Narrator: 5
A: Are you feeling better now?
B: Yes, thanks, I’ve been up and about for a couple of days.
Narrator: 6
A: Did you catch the 6.15 train?
B: Yes, but it was touch and go.
We didn’t get to the station till ten past and had to run to the platform.